Guide to the Stanford University, Office of Summer Session records
Stanford University Libraries
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of Summer Session records
1959-1967
SC0069
Stanford University. Office of Summer Session.
4 Linear feet
Office files including annual reports (1960-64), budget sheets (1962-65), faculty appointments (1962-67), publications, and announcements (1959-67) of the summer sessions.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Stanford University Libraries 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://www-sul.stanford.edu/depts/spc/spc.html
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Office of Summer Sessions, 1969.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Office files including annual reports (1960-64), budget sheets (1962-65), faculty appointments (1962-67), publications, and announcements (1959-67) of the summer sessions.
Access Terms
Stanford University--Administration.; Stanford University. Office of Summer Session.; Universities and colleges--Administration
Collection Contents
- Records, 1959-1967
  - Annual report - Presidential report - Summer session, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual report - Presidential report - Summer session, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual report, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Budget sheets, 7220 S and E, 1962 September-1963 June (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Budget sheets, 7220-00, 1963 July (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Budget sheets, 7220-00, 1963 October-1963 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Budget sheets, 7220-00, 1964 April-1964 August 15 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Budget sheets, 7220-00 S and E account, 1964 October-1965 April (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Budget - Requisitions, Account number 7-RBZ-014, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Budget - Requisitions, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Budget - Account 3903-00 - Summer Quarter Unallocated, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Budget - 3903 Account - Summer Quarter Unallocated, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Budget - Account 3903-00 - Summer Quarter Unallocated, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Budget - Account 3903-01 - Summer Quarter Unallocated Reserve, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Budget - Travel and Expense reports, 7220-00, 7220-01, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Faculty appointments - Summer session, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Faculty appointments, A-L, Summer session, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Faculty appointments, M-Z, Summer session, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Faculty appointments, A-L, Summer session, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Faculty appointments, M-Z, Summer session, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Faculty appointments, A-M, Summer session, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Faculty appointments, N-Z, Summer session, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Faculty appointments, A-L, Summer session, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Faculty appointments, M-Z, Summer session, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Visiting faculty for Summer session, Information for Bulletin, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Visiting faculty for Summer session, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Federal income tax, proposed revision, contributions, capital gains, estate and gift taxes, tax rates, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Financial aid, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Grants, fellowships, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Housing and residences, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Housing and residences, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Summer school, Humanities and Sciences, Asian languages, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Summer school, Humanities and Sciences, Asian languages, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Summer school, Humanities and Sciences, Biological sciences - Hopkins Marine Station, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Summer school, Humanities and Sciences, Modern European languages, 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Identification card and student privileges, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Identification card, student privileges, letters of invitation to Summer school sessions, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to Summer session, identification and student privilege cards, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Letter of invitation, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - School of Mathematics study group writing session, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda, Dean List, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda, Dean List, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda, Dean List, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous questionnaires, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous questionnaires, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous questions and letters, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Minott: Draft report Summer session, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Promotional material for Summer session, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Promotional material, newspaper and magazine advertising, 1963-196? (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Promotional material, newspaper and magazine advertising, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Promotion: publicity planning, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Promotion: publicity planning, finances, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Publications, brochures and flyers, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Publications, brochures and flyers, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Publications, brochures and flyers, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Summer School Bulletin, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Summer School Bulletin, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Publications, old, 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Publications, includes posters announcing Summer session activities, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Publications, includes brochures and posters, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Salary appointments - Summer session, Account 10-7220-00, and salary requisitions, 20-7220-00, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Salary appointments - Summer session, Account 10-7220-00, and salary requisitions, 20-7220-00, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Salary requisitions, Account 00-7220-00, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Special report: Statistics, enrollment, budget, 1959-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Summer Institute in Spain, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Summer Quarter Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Summer programs and conferences, old, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Summer programs and conferences, future, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Summer programs and conferences, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Summer programs and conferences, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Summer programs and conferences, general, 1959-1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Summer conference on transitional China, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Summer conferences, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Summer special program, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Transfer of funds, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tuition, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tuition, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Typing and shorthand program, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cubberley conference on education: An instrument of national goals, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - December Ford faculty seminar, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Pacific Coast Branch (PCB) of the American Historical Association Conference, 1967 Summer (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Special programs, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 8)